In an era in which the nations of
the world were waging a fierce war
of information just out of sight,
two countries were at odds with
each other: Ostania, in the east,
and Westalis, in the west.
In order to keep an eye on the actions of
a leading figure in Ostania's government
who was planning a war,
Westalis set Operation Strix in motion.
The one tasked with this operation
is the skilled agent, Twilight.
The mission given to the master of
disguise with a hundred faces was...
to start a family.
The father, Loid Forger, is a psychiatrist.
His true identity: a spy.
Code name: Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger, is a civil
servant who works at city hall.
Her true identity: an assassin.
Code name: Thorn Princess.
The daughter, Anya Forger.
Her true identity: a telepath
who can read people's minds.
The dog, Bond Forger.
His true identity: a canine seer
who can see the future.
They created this pretend
family for their own benefit,
and their mission continues as they all
hide their identities from each other.
Hello.
The customers have been served.
Oh, no. I'm heading home immediately.
My husband asked me to buy
milk and eggs on my way home.
Damn it... So she's the famous assassin
known as the Thorn Princess...
Yes. Thank you very much.
Die, you monster!
FOLLOW MAMA AND PAPA
We've just received breaking news.
Several bodies believed to belong
to members of the Red Circus
have been found in a building
in the Northern District.
The Red Circus, an extremist group
funded by foreign interests,
Papa.
I wanna watch cartoons. The news is boring.
has committed multiple
indiscriminate acts of terrorism.
No.
The authorities are investigating
this incident as one caused
There's so much information I can gather
just from a single public news outlet.
by internal strife within the group.
Next up, we have stock market news.
Okay, fine. You can change the channel.
In today's stock market,
we see a drastic drop
from where the numbers were
before the weekend...
Good morning, Bondman.
Your mission today is to
tail a certain target.
You will then find out where they
are keeping their secret weapon
So exciting.
and destroy it in order
to protect our country.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Yor—
Here—hngh—is the milk... and the eggs...
Er, uh... Thank you very much.
Um... Are you feeling unwell?
No, not exactly...
I'm just a little... No...
I can't tell him.
I absolutely cannot tell him
that I got shot in the butt
while fighting a group of armed men,
and it hurts so much!
I mean, I took care of it, but...
Sh... She was shot? By a gun?!
Mama... Are you going to die?
Don't you worry, Miss Anya.
I won't die.
I'm a bit tired, so I'm going to bed.
I'm sure that... if I get
a good night's sleep...
it'll be better in the morning... right?
Y-Yor is in a terrible mood!
Is it because I asked her to go shopping?
Yes, that must be it!
This is just a marriage of convenience,
yet I've been relying on her
too much without realizing it,
and it's upset her!
Mama won't die even if
she's been shot with a gun.
Wow.
This not good. Not good at all!
Any discord in our family will
lead to this mission failing!
I must do everything in my
power to remedy this at once!
Papa has missed the mark.
Hopefully her mood will be
better in the morning.
It didn't get better.
Good morning.
G-Good morning...
Ow...
I... I need to brighten her mood!
Yor! We're both off today, so...
Why don't we go on a date?
A d-d...
I want to thank you for always helping
me with raising Anya and the chores.
I'd like you to relax to the utmost today.
A date...
My boyfriend took me out
on a cruise the other day!
What kind of dates do you go on, Yor?
Huh? I've never been on one.
No way. Surely you and
your husband go on dates.
Oh, uh, um...
I must at least experience
this thing they call a "date,"
or someone may suspect that
we're a pretend family.
Um... We don't have to go
if you're not feeling well.
I will go!
I would like to take this opportunity
to learn everything that I can!
Learn?
I'll go change right away!
Anya wants to go, too!
Dates are so exciting!
Er, sorry, but you're staying home.
Because it's a date.
Shock!
Poo...
Borf...
All right, be good while we're gone.
C'mere a sec.
Okay, hang on! How many
times do I have to tell you?!
I'm an informant, not your errand boy!
I had no other choice.
I can't leave Anya home alone,
and this is a very important mission to
ensure that we remain one happy family.
You said you wanted to create
some new spy gadgets, didn't you?
I've already prepared you a check. Here.
Must you take advantage of
my weakness every single time?!
All right, let's go, Yor.
Allow me to take your hand.
Last night, I came up with 862 date
plans to ensure that Yor has fun.
There's no way I could fail.
Um... I'm terribly sorry, Loid...
Sitting down would mean my
butt will be in even more pain.
But I'd prefer if we just
walked around on this date.
Huh?! She's mad?!
She's still mad?!
This just killed 794 of those plans!
O-Of course.
Then let's just take a casual little stroll.
I'm worried about Mama and Papa.
Well, if they've got a kid like you
worried about them, they're screwed.
Come on and watch some
cartoons inside, kiddo.
Go, Bondman!
Follow him and protect world peace!
Scruffy Head!
Huh?
I want to tail Mama and Papa!
What the hell? That sounds like
some epic fun! Let's do it!
Let's tail them!
But your Papa's pretty sharp,
so we're gonna have to be careful
and wear some disguises!
Yep!
I think you're bringing even more
attention to yourself in that getup.
No problemo.
Right...
You've been charged with
guarding this house,
highly skilled agents of the
Secret Organization P2!
Bond, Director Chimera,
and Agent Penguinman!
Twilight, I'm gonna get a good
look at the romance skills
that have landed you countless women!
I can't read their minds.
They're too far away.
What are those two doing?
Spotted them instantly
Is she pretending to be a spy again?
How is that even fun?
Anyway, I'll just think of this as part
of the mission to keep our happy family,
and pretend I haven't noticed.
I'm sure she'll be fine
since Franky's with her.
Loid?
Oh, er, it's nothing.
More importantly, I need
to brighten her mood.
Why don't we go shopping?
Central Mall
You have such a striking figure, Yor.
I'm sure you'd look great in pants, too.
Would you like to try these on?
If I wear anything that tight,
it'll agitate my wound,
and I'll pass out in agony.
I can't.
Huh? Oh... I'm sorry.
Movie Theater
Oh, my beloved!
Please look me in the eyes
and tell me you're lying!
Yor...
I won't let anyone else have
your beautiful, proud soul!
You might make a scene.
Maybe you should sit down?
No, I'm fine.
If I sit down, my butt...
Club
Yor, it's dangerous to stand up...
Pond at the Park
But if I sit down, my butt...
Spa
Huh?
Zoo
My butt...
What should I do? I can't
concentrate on this date at all.
And here Loid is trying to
teach me so many things!
What should I do?
I think her mood is getting
worse rather than better!
Am I somehow picking all
the wrong things to do?
What is it?! What exactly does Yor like?!
Did I not do enough research?!
Loid always tries to act cool,
but he's failing left and right.
Scruffy, scruffy, scruff. What a loser!
Scruffy Head, does your personality suck?
No!
As someone who can't get any girls, it's my
absolute right to ridicule him right now!
You poor thing.
What'd you say, you little—
They're starting to become a distraction.
I'm sure you're a bit tired,
so why don't we have dinner?
All right.
Ah, you must be Mister Forger.
Please, have a seat.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
We have a strict dress
code at our restaurant,
and we also do not allow guests under
eighteen into our establishment.
Well, you heard the guy. Give it up.
Let's start heading home.
I'm getting kinda bored.
Th-Thorn Princess?! What the
hell is she doing here?!
What's up? You lookin' for a bathroom?
There's no doubt about it.
Ow!
That's the assassin woman who
raided our hideout yesterday!
What's she doing here?
When I survived that tragedy,
I took it as God's mercy on my soul,
and I decided to turn over a
new leaf and get a proper job
for the sake of the girlfriend
I live with, too!
I see. I see how it is, my comrades in hell.
I just need to kill her, right?
I'll avenge the Red Circus!
There's a bad guy in the restaurant!
Die, Thorn Princess!
Hurgh! That's right! You're the
best assassin ever! I am defeated!
Y-Yor, you're an assassin?
Let's get a divorce.
The Forgers are done.
Let's get rid of Anya, too.
Come on. Let's get goin', kiddo.
No!
What? Are we still playing this game?
My family's in danger!
Huh?
Wait, is she worried that her parents
might get divorced or something?
She feels that strongly
about a pretend family?
O-Okay, fine... I guess I'll play
this game with you a little longer.
Okay, our next game is called "Infiltration"!
Infillytration!
Would you like an aperitif?
I'll have a glass of dry champagne.
I'll just take a cocktail. Any is fine.
This restaurant serves a very rare delicacy
called "blowfish" from the far east.
I hear they serve it in
one of their courses, too.
W-Wow...
Blowfish is highly poisonous,
but I'm told its flesh is quite exquisite.
Pardon, could you take this
to the lady at table 3?
Right away.
Drink a whole fish's worth of blowfish
poison and go to hell, Thorn Princess!
Scruffy Head, hurry!
You can't rush this.
We gotta be careful when we're infiltrating.
Get too loud, and they'll find us.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, my. This has quite the color and aroma.
And it's so thick.
Mama, you can't drink that!
Huh? I feel...
I've avenged you, my brothers.
It's like the pain in my butt has
gone away! I feel so much better!
This woman had built up immunity to poisons.
Though my whole body
does feel a bit tingly.
But I can sit down!
I'm starting to get really hungry.
I'm very excited to eat here.
Huh? Right...
Is she in a better mood?
Is it because of the drink?
Huh? Wait... I'm pretty sure
I put in enough to kill her. What?
* Blowfish poison is very dangerous, so please don't try this at home
There's a fine line between
poison and medicine.
Ordinary people should
take recommended doses
and follow directions
when using medication.
What's wrong?
I guess I'll have to take
things into my own hands.
I'll just finish her off myself!
I should be able to build a makeshift
bomb with the stuff in storage.
With that and that and that...
THAT
I won't be able to include a timer,
so I'll just have to run into her with it.
I'm sorry, Catherine.
Please forgive me for being such a fool.
We'll be right above the dining hall soon.
Once we're right above,
I'll lower you down on a wire,
and you can hear what they're
talking about... Huh?
I should be able to make the
bomb's body with **** and ****.
I'm pretty sure they were
on the right-hand shelf.
After I put in the blue **** that's
on the opposite shelf and some ****.
To make sure I get the most out of it,
I'll need to include ****, too!
Okay, this should work!
Damn it! What is this?
Olive oil?
Who the hell spilled this here?
Damn it! I don't have time for this!
Washtub!
Who the hell set up a prank like this?
That's a perfect container for the bomb.
Wait, this is a bit too small.
Huh? Hey, wait... Huh?!
Why was there an already-completed bomb here?
And what are these? Peanuts?
A peanut bomb?!
Wait...
Are they working with the Thorn Princess?
Huh?
A kid?
Red Circus guy.
She knows who I am?
If you've learned your lesson,
stay away from An—from us.
Got it? There won't be a next time.
You need to completely
give up being a bad guy...
and make Cathurin a happy lady.
She even knows about Catherine?!
I guess she saw right through me...
Thorn Princess is a fearsome foe.
I can't believe she's got an insane
kid like that working for her, too.
We live in completely different worlds.
I'm not cut out for this.
I'm going to forget all this
and live a normal life.
The atmosphere in that
restaurant was quite lively.
But everything was so delicious!
Yes.
Thank goodness. She seems
to be in a much better mood.
I think I was able to protect the
peace of the Forgers for now.
This is all thanks to Anya. Heh.
So, hey... Where'd you run off to earlier?
Thank you very much, Loid.
Ever since I was little, I spent most of my
time taking care of my brother or working,
so I rarely ever had a chance to have fun.
So...
You made me really happy today.
If it's not too much trouble,
please invite me out again sometime.
When I'm not injured.
I would love to. Anytime.
Oh, look! There's a traveling
amusement park over there!
It might close soon, but let's go see it anyway.
Papa! Anya wants to go
on the Ferris wheel, too!
And the amusement park!
Hey, wait! I thought we were
tailing them! Are we done?!
Why, though?!
The medicine (poison) had worn off
The medicine—that is,
the poison—had worn off.
I don't understand women.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
BOND'S STRATEGY TO STAY ALIVE
DAMIAN'S FIELD RESEARCH TRIP